{
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "choice",
      "question": "What is the capital of France?",
      "correct": "1",
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Berlin"
        },
        {
          "1": "Paris"
        },
        {
          "2": "London"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "choice",
      "question": "Where does the Queen of England live?",
      "correct": "0",
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "London"
        },
        {
          "1": "Paris"
        },
        {
          "2": "Berlin"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "choice",
      "question": "What's the spanish word for father??",
      "correct": "2",
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Madre"
        },
        {
          "1": "Novio"
        },
        {
          "2": "Padre"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "choice",
      "question": "What type of factory did Willy Wonka own?",
      "correct": "1",
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Bicycle"
        },
        {
          "1": "Chocolate"
        },
        {
          "2": "Car"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "What colour is the sky?",
      "correct": "blue"
    },
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "What African herbivore has four legs and a very long neck?",
      "correct": "giraffe"
    },
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "In the day we see the sun, at night we see the _______?",
      "correct": "moon"
    },
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "What artist came out with the song Toxic?",
      "correct": "britney spears"
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Which numbers are prime?",
      "correct": [
        0,
        1
      ],
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "17"
        },
        {
          "1": "3"
        },
        {
          "2": "2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Which two characters are wizards?",
      "correct": [
        0,
        2
      ],
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Harry Potter"
        },
        {
          "1": "Shrek"
        },
        {
          "2": "Dumbledore"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mutliple",
      "question": "What ingredients are in a BLT?",
      "correct": [
        0,
        1,
        2
      ],
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Bacon"
        },
        {
          "1": "Lettuce"
        },
        {
          "2": "Tomato"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Which songs are by Lady Gaga?",
      "correct": [
        1,
        2
      ],
      "answers": [
        {
          "0": "Jingle Bells"
        },
        {
          "1": "Born This Way"
        },
        {
          "2": "Poker Face"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
